export var hiragana = [{prompt: 'あ', unicode: '\\u3042', answers: ['a']},
{prompt: 'い', unicode: '\\u3044', answers: ['i']},
{prompt: 'う', unicode: '\\u3046', answers: ['u']},
{prompt: 'え', unicode: '\\u3048', answers: ['e']},
{prompt: 'お', unicode: '\\u304A', answers: ['o']},
{prompt: 'か', unicode: '\\u304B', answers: ['ka']},
{prompt: 'が', unicode: '\\u304C', answers: ['ga']},
{prompt: 'き', unicode: '\\u304D', answers: ['ki']},
{prompt: 'きゃ', unicode: '\\u304D\\u3083', answers: ['kya']},
{prompt: 'きゅ', unicode: '\\u304D\\u3085', answers: ['kyu']},
{prompt: 'きょ', unicode: '\\u304D\\u3087', answers: ['kyo']},
{prompt: 'ぎ', unicode: '\\u304E', answers: ['gi']},
{prompt: 'ぎゃ', unicode: '\\u304E\\u3083', answers: ['gya']},
{prompt: 'ぎゅ', unicode: '\\u304E\\u3085', answers: ['gyu']},
{prompt: 'ぎょ', unicode: '\\u304E\\u3087', answers: ['gyo']},
{prompt: 'く', unicode: '\\u304F', answers: ['ku']},
{prompt: 'ぐ', unicode: '\\u3050', answers: ['gu']},
{prompt: 'け', unicode: '\\u3051', answers: ['ke']},
{prompt: 'げ', unicode: '\\u3052', answers: ['ge']},
{prompt: 'こ', unicode: '\\u3053', answers: ['ko']},
{prompt: 'ご', unicode: '\\u3054', answers: ['go']},
{prompt: 'さ', unicode: '\\u3055', answers: ['sa']},
{prompt: 'ざ', unicode: '\\u3056', answers: ['za']},
{prompt: 'し', unicode: '\\u3057', answers: ['shi']},
{prompt: 'しゃ', unicode: '\\u3057\\u3083', answers: ['sha']},
{prompt: 'しゅ', unicode: '\\u3057\\u3085', answers: ['shu']},
{prompt: 'しょ', unicode: '\\u3057\\u3087', answers: ['sho']},
{prompt: 'じ', unicode: '\\u3058', answers: ['ji']},
{prompt: 'じゃ', unicode: '\\u3058\\u3083', answers: ['jya']},
{prompt: 'じゅ', unicode: '\\u3058\\u3085', answers: ['jyu']},
{prompt: 'じょ', unicode: '\\u3058\\u3087', answers: ['jyo']},
{prompt: 'す', unicode: '\\u3059', answers: ['su']},
{prompt: 'ず', unicode: '\\u305A', answers: ['zu']},
{prompt: 'せ', unicode: '\\u305B', answers: ['se']},
{prompt: 'ぜ', unicode: '\\u305C', answers: ['ze']},
{prompt: 'そ', unicode: '\\u305D', answers: ['so']},
{prompt: 'ぞ', unicode: '\\u305E', answers: ['zo']},
{prompt: 'た', unicode: '\\u305F', answers: ['ta']},
{prompt: 'だ', unicode: '\\u3060', answers: ['da']},
{prompt: 'ち', unicode: '\\u3061', answers: ['chi']},
{prompt: 'ちゃ', unicode: '\\u3061\\u3083', answers: ['cha']},
{prompt: 'ちゅ', unicode: '\\u3061\\u3085', answers: ['chu']},
{prompt: 'ちょ', unicode: '\\u3061\\u3087', answers: ['cho']},
{prompt: 'ぢ', unicode: '\\u3062', answers: ['dzi']},
{prompt: 'ぢゃ', unicode: '\\u3062\\u3083', answers: ['dzya']},
{prompt: 'ぢゅ', unicode: '\\u3062\\u3085', answers: ['dzyu']},
{prompt: 'ぢょ', unicode: '\\u3062\\u3087', answers: ['dzyo']},
{prompt: 'つ', unicode: '\\u3064', answers: ['tsu']},
{prompt: 'づ', unicode: '\\u3065', answers: ['dzu']},
{prompt: 'て', unicode: '\\u3066', answers: ['te']},
{prompt: 'で', unicode: '\\u3067', answers: ['de']},
{prompt: 'と', unicode: '\\u3068', answers: ['to']},
{prompt: 'ど', unicode: '\\u3069', answers: ['do']},
{prompt: 'な', unicode: '\\u306A', answers: ['na']},
{prompt: 'に', unicode: '\\u306B', answers: ['ni']},
{prompt: 'にゃ', unicode: '\\u306B\\u3083', answers: ['nya']},
{prompt: 'にゅ', unicode: '\\u306B\\u3085', answers: ['nyu']},
{prompt: 'にょ', unicode: '\\u306B\\u3087', answers: ['nyo']},
{prompt: 'ぬ', unicode: '\\u306C', answers: ['nu']},
{prompt: 'ね', unicode: '\\u306D', answers: ['ne']},
{prompt: 'の', unicode: '\\u306E', answers: ['no']},
{prompt: 'は', unicode: '\\u306F', answers: ['ha']},
{prompt: 'ば', unicode: '\\u3070', answers: ['ba']},
{prompt: 'ぱ', unicode: '\\u3071', answers: ['pa']},
{prompt: 'ひ', unicode: '\\u3072', answers: ['hi']},
{prompt: 'ひゃ', unicode: '\\u3072\\u3083', answers: ['hya']},
{prompt: 'ひゅ', unicode: '\\u3072\\u3085', answers: ['hyu']},
{prompt: 'ひょ', unicode: '\\u3072\\u3087', answers: ['hyo']},
{prompt: 'び', unicode: '\\u3073', answers: ['bi']},
{prompt: 'びゃ', unicode: '\\u3073\\u3083', answers: ['bya']},
{prompt: 'びゅ', unicode: '\\u3073\\u3085', answers: ['byu']},
{prompt: 'びょ', unicode: '\\u3073\\u3087', answers: ['byo']},
{prompt: 'ぴ', unicode: '\\u3074', answers: ['pi']},
{prompt: 'ぴゃ', unicode: '\\u3074\\u3083', answers: ['pya']},
{prompt: 'ぴゅ', unicode: '\\u3074\\u3085', answers: ['pyu']},
{prompt: 'ぴょ', unicode: '\\u3074\\u3087', answers: ['pyo']},
{prompt: 'ふ', unicode: '\\u3075', answers: ['fu']},
{prompt: 'ぶ', unicode: '\\u3076', answers: ['bu']},
{prompt: 'ぷ', unicode: '\\u3077', answers: ['pu']},
{prompt: 'へ', unicode: '\\u3078', answers: ['he']},
{prompt: 'べ', unicode: '\\u3079', answers: ['be']},
{prompt: 'ぺ', unicode: '\\u307A', answers: ['pe']},
{prompt: 'ほ', unicode: '\\u307B', answers: ['ho']},
{prompt: 'ぼ', unicode: '\\u307C', answers: ['bo']},
{prompt: 'ぽ', unicode: '\\u307D', answers: ['po']},
{prompt: 'ま', unicode: '\\u307E', answers: ['ma']},
{prompt: 'み', unicode: '\\u307F', answers: ['mi']},
{prompt: 'みゃ', unicode: '\\u307F\\u3083', answers: ['mya']},
{prompt: 'みゅ', unicode: '\\u307F\\u3085', answers: ['myu']},
{prompt: 'みょ', unicode: '\\u307F\\u3087', answers: ['myo']},
{prompt: 'む', unicode: '\\u3080', answers: ['mu']},
{prompt: 'め', unicode: '\\u3081', answers: ['me']},
{prompt: 'も', unicode: '\\u3082', answers: ['mo']},
{prompt: 'や', unicode: '\\u3084', answers: ['ya']},
{prompt: 'ゆ', unicode: '\\u3086', answers: ['yu']},
{prompt: 'よ', unicode: '\\u3088', answers: ['yo']},
{prompt: 'ら', unicode: '\\u3089', answers: ['ra']},
{prompt: 'り', unicode: '\\u308A', answers: ['ri']},
{prompt: 'りゃ', unicode: '\\u308A\\u3083', answers: ['rya']},
{prompt: 'りゅ', unicode: '\\u308A\\u3085', answers: ['ryu']},
{prompt: 'りょ', unicode: '\\u308A\\u3087', answers: ['ryo']},
{prompt: 'る', unicode: '\\u308B', answers: ['ru']},
{prompt: 'れ', unicode: '\\u308C', answers: ['re']},
{prompt: 'ろ', unicode: '\\u308D', answers: ['ro']},
{prompt: 'わ', unicode: '\\u308F', answers: ['wa']},
{prompt: 'を', unicode: '\\u3092', answers: ['wo']},
{prompt: 'ん', unicode: '\\u3093', answers: ['n']}];
export var katakana = [
{prompt: 'ア', unicode: '\\u30A2', answers: ['a']},
{prompt: 'イ', unicode: '\\u30A4', answers: ['i']},
{prompt: 'ウ', unicode: '\\u30A6', answers: ['u']},
{prompt: 'エ', unicode: '\\u30A8', answers: ['e']},
{prompt: 'オ', unicode: '\\u30AA', answers: ['o']},
{prompt: 'カ', unicode: '\\u30AB', answers: ['ka']},
{prompt: 'ガ', unicode: '\\u30AC', answers: ['ga']},
{prompt: 'キ', unicode: '\\u30AD', answers: ['ki']},
{prompt: 'キャ', unicode: '\\u30AD\\u30E3', answers: ['kya']},
{prompt: 'キュ', unicode: '\\u30AD\\u30E5', answers: ['kyu']},
{prompt: 'キョ', unicode: '\\u30AD\\u30E7', answers: ['kyo']},
{prompt: 'ギ', unicode: '\\u30AE', answers: ['gi']},
{prompt: 'ギャ', unicode: '\\u30AE\\u30E3', answers: ['gya']},
{prompt: 'ギュ', unicode: '\\u30AE\\u30E5', answers: ['gyu']},
{prompt: 'ギョ', unicode: '\\u30AE\\u30E7', answers: ['gyo']},
{prompt: 'ク', unicode: '\\u30AF', answers: ['ku']},
{prompt: 'グ', unicode: '\\u30B0', answers: ['gu']},
{prompt: 'ケ', unicode: '\\u30B1', answers: ['ke']},
{prompt: 'ゲ', unicode: '\\u30B2', answers: ['ge']},
{prompt: 'コ', unicode: '\\u30B3', answers: ['ko']},
{prompt: 'ゴ', unicode: '\\u30B4', answers: ['go']},
{prompt: 'サ', unicode: '\\u30B5', answers: ['sa']},
{prompt: 'ザ', unicode: '\\u30B6', answers: ['za']},
{prompt: 'シ', unicode: '\\u30B7', answers: ['shi']},
{prompt: 'シャ', unicode: '\\u30B7\\u30E3', answers: ['sha']},
{prompt: 'シュ', unicode: '\\u30B7\\u30E5', answers: ['shu']},
{prompt: 'ショ', unicode: '\\u30B7\\u30E7', answers: ['sho']},
{prompt: 'ジ', unicode: '\\u30B8', answers: ['ji']},
{prompt: 'ジャ', unicode: '\\u30B8\\u30E3', answers: ['jya']},
{prompt: 'ジュ', unicode: '\\u30B8\\u30E5', answers: ['jyu']},
{prompt: 'ジョ', unicode: '\\u30B8\\u30E7', answers: ['jyo']},
{prompt: 'ス', unicode: '\\u30B9', answers: ['su']},
{prompt: 'ズ', unicode: '\\u30BA', answers: ['zu']},
{prompt: 'セ', unicode: '\\u30BB', answers: ['se']},
{prompt: 'ゼ', unicode: '\\u30BC', answers: ['ze']},
{prompt: 'ソ', unicode: '\\u30BD', answers: ['so']},
{prompt: 'ゾ', unicode: '\\u30BE', answers: ['zo']},
{prompt: 'タ', unicode: '\\u30BF', answers: ['ta']},
{prompt: 'ダ', unicode: '\\u30C0', answers: ['da']},
{prompt: 'チ', unicode: '\\u30C1', answers: ['chi']},
{prompt: 'チャ', unicode: '\\u30C1\\u30E3', answers: ['cha']},
{prompt: 'チュ', unicode: '\\u30C1\\u30E5', answers: ['chu']},
{prompt: 'チョ', unicode: '\\u30C1\\u30E7', answers: ['cho']},
{prompt: 'ヂ', unicode: '\\u30C2', answers: ['dzi']},
{prompt: 'ヂャ', unicode: '\\u30C2\\u30E3', answers: ['dzya']},
{prompt: 'ヂュ', unicode: '\\u30C2\\u30E5', answers: ['dzyu']},
{prompt: 'ヂョ', unicode: '\\u30C2\\u30E7', answers: ['dzyo']},
{prompt: 'ツ', unicode: '\\u30C4', answers: ['tsu']},
{prompt: 'ヅ', unicode: '\\u30C5', answers: ['dzu']},
{prompt: 'テ', unicode: '\\u30C6', answers: ['te']},
{prompt: 'デ', unicode: '\\u30C7', answers: ['de']},
{prompt: 'ト', unicode: '\\u30C8', answers: ['to']},
{prompt: 'ド', unicode: '\\u30C9', answers: ['do']},
{prompt: 'ナ', unicode: '\\u30CA', answers: ['na']},
{prompt: 'ニ', unicode: '\\u30CB', answers: ['ni']},
{prompt: 'ニャ', unicode: '\\u30CB\\u30E3', answers: ['nya']},
{prompt: 'ニュ', unicode: '\\u30CB\\u30E5', answers: ['nyu']},
{prompt: 'ニョ', unicode: '\\u30CB\\u30E7', answers: ['nyo']},
{prompt: 'ヌ', unicode: '\\u30CC', answers: ['nu']},
{prompt: 'ネ', unicode: '\\u30CD', answers: ['ne']},
{prompt: 'ノ', unicode: '\\u30CE', answers: ['no']},
{prompt: 'ハ', unicode: '\\u30CF', answers: ['ha']},
{prompt: 'バ', unicode: '\\u30D0', answers: ['ba']},
{prompt: 'パ', unicode: '\\u30D1', answers: ['pa']},
{prompt: 'ヒ', unicode: '\\u30D2', answers: ['hi']},
{prompt: 'ヒャ', unicode: '\\u30D2\\u30E3', answers: ['hya']},
{prompt: 'ヒュ', unicode: '\\u30D2\\u30E5', answers: ['hyu']},
{prompt: 'ヒョ', unicode: '\\u30D2\\u30E7', answers: ['hyo']},
{prompt: 'ビ', unicode: '\\u30D3', answers: ['bi']},
{prompt: 'ビャ', unicode: '\\u30D3\\u30E3', answers: ['bya']},
{prompt: 'ビュ', unicode: '\\u30D3\\u30E5', answers: ['byu']},
{prompt: 'ビョ', unicode: '\\u30D3\\u30E7', answers: ['byo']},
{prompt: 'ピ', unicode: '\\u30D4', answers: ['pi']},
{prompt: 'ピャ', unicode: '\\u30D4\\u30E3', answers: ['pya']},
{prompt: 'ピュ', unicode: '\\u30D4\\u30E5', answers: ['pyu']},
{prompt: 'ピョ', unicode: '\\u30D4\\u30E7', answers: ['pyo']},
{prompt: 'フ', unicode: '\\u30D5', answers: ['fu']},
{prompt: 'ブ', unicode: '\\u30D6', answers: ['bu']},
{prompt: 'プ', unicode: '\\u30D7', answers: ['pu']},
{prompt: 'ヘ', unicode: '\\u30D8', answers: ['he']},
{prompt: 'ベ', unicode: '\\u30D9', answers: ['be']},
{prompt: 'ペ', unicode: '\\u30DA', answers: ['pe']},
{prompt: 'ホ', unicode: '\\u30DB', answers: ['ho']},
{prompt: 'ボ', unicode: '\\u30DC', answers: ['bo']},
{prompt: 'ポ', unicode: '\\u30DD', answers: ['po']},
{prompt: 'マ', unicode: '\\u30DE', answers: ['ma']},
{prompt: 'ミ', unicode: '\\u30DF', answers: ['mi']},
{prompt: 'ミャ', unicode: '\\u30DF\\u30E3', answers: ['mya']},
{prompt: 'ミュ', unicode: '\\u30DF\\u30E5', answers: ['myu']},
{prompt: 'ミョ', unicode: '\\u30DF\\u30E7', answers: ['myo']},
{prompt: 'ム', unicode: '\\u30E0', answers: ['mu']},
{prompt: 'メ', unicode: '\\u30E1', answers: ['me']},
{prompt: 'モ', unicode: '\\u30E2', answers: ['mo']},
{prompt: 'ヤ', unicode: '\\u30E4', answers: ['ya']},
{prompt: 'ユ', unicode: '\\u30E6', answers: ['yu']},
{prompt: 'ヨ', unicode: '\\u30E8', answers: ['yo']},
{prompt: 'ラ', unicode: '\\u30E9', answers: ['ra']},
{prompt: 'リ', unicode: '\\u30EA', answers: ['ri']},
{prompt: 'リャ', unicode: '\\u30EA\\u30E3', answers: ['rya']},
{prompt: 'リュ', unicode: '\\u30EA\\u30E5', answers: ['ryu']},
{prompt: 'リョ', unicode: '\\u30EA\\u30E7', answers: ['ryo']},
{prompt: 'ル', unicode: '\\u30EB', answers: ['ru']},
{prompt: 'レ', unicode: '\\u30EC', answers: ['re']},
{prompt: 'ロ', unicode: '\\u30ED', answers: ['ro']},
{prompt: 'ワ', unicode: '\\u30EF', answers: ['wa']},
{prompt: 'ヲ', unicode: '\\u30F2', answers: ['wo']},
{prompt: 'ン', unicode: '\\u30F3', answers: ['n']}]